

PETER HARRISON

PO Box 1100, Zephyr Cove, NV 89448 +1 775 230 4266

peter.harrison@harrisoncareers.com
Linkedin. https://uk.linkedin.com/in/peter-harrison-careers

SUMMARY

Careers counselling expert, who has worked for some of the world's most prestigious employers, including Goldman Sachs, McKinsey and Deloitte. Run an elite team with a 15+ year track-record of helping clients to win thousands of job offers in Technology, Finance, Banking, Consulting, Accounting, Law and other industries.

EXPERIENCE

PETER HARRISON CAREERS LLC, Nevada, USA Founder & CEO

2002-present

- Founded an independent careers service that helps candidates get jobs with world-class employers in the technology, investment banking, management consulting, law and accounting industries.
- 100% track-record of successfully helping every client get hired.

DIVERSITYNOW LIMITED, London, UK

1999-2009

Founder & Managing Director

- Founded a niche recruitment agency that coordinated a careers network for black students and black professionals, helping them to get jobs with world-class employers. Built the largest black careers network in Europe.
- Developed strong business relationships with Goldman Sachs, McKinsey, Accenture, KPMG and Barclays.
- Drove company from scratch to a valuation of £8,000,000 within a year of operation.

GOLDMAN SACHS INTERNATIONAL, London, UK

1993-2000

Executive Director, Equities Division – Convertible Bond Sales

- Survived 47 grueling interviews by GS directors in Chicago, New York and London to land my job offer. Also offered associate jobs by Morgan Stanley, Credit Suisse, UBS, Deutsche Bank and Merrill Lynch.
- Built a successful franchise from scratch, selling convertible bonds to UK clients.
- Cold called >3,000 asset managers to pitch new issues; appointed Head of team servicing Scottish asset managers.
- Selected to head European Equities Recruiting for 1995-97; interviewed approximately 1,300 candidates over 7 years.

MCKINSEY & COMPANY, London, UK Summer Associate

1992

• One of only 22 interns hired from 410 Kellogg candidates. Evaluated strategic implications of breaking up British Gas.

DELOITTE (formerly Arthur Andersen), Edinburgh, UK

1989-1991

Auditor & Tax Consultant

Offered Deloitte job at a premium salary immediately after first ever interview. Also offered jobs by 10 other firms.

QUALIFICATIONS

1994
1993
1992
1989
1989
1986

OTHER DATA

Track-record, unmatched by any other competitor, of getting multiple hundreds of clients hired by the world's best companies, and a history of getting job offers from (almost!) every company I have ever applied to.

Qualifications: one of the UK's most highly-qualified young professionals, having achieved the ACA, CTA, AIIMR (now the CFA) and ACT qualifications by the age of 25.

Personal: Highly-successful real estate investor. Dedicated family man. Enjoy speed and risk (motorbikes, skiing, rock climbing). Run 1,000 miles each year. Spent my youth working on building sites and farms.